Eco Aqualome
Eco Aqualume
It's dark! Are there fish?
Is it a river fish?
I like river fish.
I like it.
It's cute.
What do you think? I knew it. Fish on the move.
They're so cute.
I'm so happy.
I can't eat fish, so raw fish.
I didn't know there was a time like this.
It's a time when river fish are full of life.
You can't tell them apart at all.
I wish people would say that river fish are more subdued in color.
Oh, it's an ayu.
See the yellowish ones?
Yellowish tail, that's an ayu.
It's tiny.
It's a juvenile. It's going to grow up.
Big eyes. So cute.
It's a carp.
Koi?
Carp don't have stomachs.
Why not?
They don't have a satiety center, so they can eat as much as they want.
That's why they grow so big.
Are these ornaments?
This is a carp.
It's alive.
It's stuck.
Oh, my God! I love it.
This is a bigfin reef squid.
It's a bluefin squid.
Aeon, you just scared the shit out of me.Aon was so surprised.
Are you a squid?
I'm a squid.
What do you like?
They're called capelinids, but the opposite.
It's got no legs and no head.
If you put them together like a human...
I'm not sure.
There are a few theories.
I think they communicate with other individuals
By changing the color of their bodies.
I've heard it said that they communicate with other animals.
He's smart.
What's your score on the Toic?
Twick just doesn't do it.
If he did, he could.
That's great.
What a card.
How many times can you get in a chain?
Ricoheki, genius.
Something smells really bad.
Oh, my God!
Cards.
After all, it's a unique atmosphere after closing time, isn't it?
Yes, yes.
Wow, there are so many.
There are so many. This is the ocean.
There are so many.
What is this?
I wonder if they are horse mackerels.
I like horse mackerel omelet.
I like horse mackerel omelets.
Oh, there's an utsubo, too.
Which one?
This one, this one.This, this, this.
This one.
He's not here. Oh, that one.
Yeah, this is a depression.
Uh, a depression.
Oh, there's one here. There's one here, too.
Oh, there they are.
They're not so fancy, but...
Interesting shape, though.
Depressives have two jaws because they are weak at swallowing.
First, there is a jaw at the mouth,
The other jaw is in the belly,
The first jaw is at the mouth, and the second jaw is at the stomach, so it grabs the rice and puts it into the stomach.
So, the fish has two jaws.
It is a big fish. I wonder if it's a roanie horse mackerel.
Horse mackerel.
It's a silver horse mackerel.
Oh, they are horse mackerels.
I didn't know they were this big.
They are huge.
I saw this big bluefin jack when I went scuba diving last time.
Do you scuba?
I did scuba diving.
For real?
Scuba diving.
I got my license last year.
I really wanted to get my license right before Mowan, so I went to a training camp.
I don't know.
It was the only way.
I went to the training camp after the final was decided.
I was surprised.
I was so surprised.
I'm sure I won't catch a cold.
Please, I'm really begging you.
Just the injury.
Please just leave me alone.He said to just leave the injury.
I'm scared of active, sober people.
Stop it.
I'm scared of the active person who doesn't look like an active person.
I'm scared.
You're active like that?
I like to dive and fish.
I want to see fish.
That's not the goal.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, what's that?
Oh, it's a ray.
Stingrays.
There's a ray... it's behind the rock right now.
Is that what I think it is?
Is that, uh, white?
There's a white ray.
Is that a white ray?
That's amazing.
Call it an albinos.
It's really white.
That's cool.
Albinos.
Cool albinos.
I think it's rare.
Look at that.
Jellyfish.
How about jellyfish?
I think I like jellyfish a lot.
I like jellyfish a lot.
They heal me.
Look at them.
Good, good, good.
That's a lot of jellyfish.That's a lot of water.
This is water.
This is a water jellyfish often said to live in Japan.
It's so relaxing.
Do you see the four-leaf clover-like thing here?
I can see it.
This is the stomach.
It's right there.
So, if you look closely, you can see that there are dots in these four places,
Like this one.
This is where they put the rice.
You eat rice?
Rice, yes, yes, yes. They eat rice.
Plankton and so on.
It is taken there and digested here.
It has four stomachs.
Yes, yes, there are four stomachs.
So, eat a lot of food there.
Nutrients come from there.
What is this?
Bisenkurage.
What the hell is this?
I'm reading the description clearly.
I want you to explain it to me.
I don't understand.
I don't know what this is.
I don't know.
He says you can eat it.
I hear it's edible.
Is it delicious?
Jellyfish is delicious, isn't it?
Have you ever eaten jellyfish?
Jellyfish.
Jellyfish is a mushroom.
It's a mushroom.
It's a mushroom.It's a mushroom, that's what it is.
I thought it was a jellyfish.
Jellyfish are mushrooms.
Such a neat and straight.
Cute.
So straight.
I'm happy.
But wait.
New revelation.
There's a Chinese dish of stir-fried kikurage.
I love it so much, my little one loves kikurage.
It's delicious, isn't it, kikurage?
Mushrooms.
I like mushrooms.
Straight.
It's nice, this one.
American willow jellyfish.
Beautiful, the color.
I still like the way it's conked out.
Clear orange.
Cute.
It's cute and retro.
Retro color.
Good eye candy, that's what it is.
They call it retro.
I'm glad to hear that.
Jellyfish?
You call this retro,
I'm glad you call it retro.
Everything is getting shallow.
Since a while ago.
Maybe it's the tone of voice.
I wonder if I can't get away with a tone of voice.
A white dog.A white dog.
A white dolphin.
It's called a beluga.
Can I go down there?
Wow, it's huge.
I noticed.
Wow.
That's a beluga.
This is very picturesque.
It's very picturesque, isn't it?
He has a kind face, doesn't he?
He's got a kind face.
White dolphins are known as the canaries of the sea.
They are famous for their various voices.
This flabby thing here is called a melon.
They make it tremble.
It makes a sound like an ultrasonic wave.
It's a melon.
Are you sure it's called a white dolphin?
One... beluga.
I think it's Russian for "white.
I'm sorry, I'm not sure.
White?
I think "beluga" means white.
No, it's not.
I've been looking at it a lot.
Oh, my God.
You have a New Anna face.
New Anna.
How about a New Anna face?
It's so picturesque.
It's like a scene from a movie.
With the white anus.
It's over.
It's over tomorrow.
You should face him.You should face him.
There's a bunch of them.
That's a hell of an aquarium.
Wow, we're way past the flatline.
You're about to say that. Why aren't we there yet?
You're smart. Are you smart?
Smart, very smart.
I'm sure you just got that information from the staff, from me.
Are you smart? I'm smart.
That doesn't make any sense.
Have you ever seen a bubbling ring? You know, the dolphins?
You know, the white dolphin with the mouth cancer?
Bubble rings are made by applying a certain...
What do you think it is? It starts suddenly.
Bubbling is the application of a certain behavior to bubbling.
It's not a cigarette? It's not a cigarette.
You see a person smoking, you see a bubbling ring here.
The mortician? I'm not a mortician.
I don't smoke mortician in Camosy.
What do you mean?
The answer is, you blow on them to scour the bottom of the ocean for crabs and stuff.
You blow on them. You breathe on them.
You blow on them and then you eat the shellfish that come up.
I heard it was used as a ring.
Or not.
Did it become a ring?
Maybe it did, maybe it didn't.
I've just been a little fuzzy on the subject all day.
Did you get it?
Was it?
Yes, you're right.
Good. Correct.
You were half right.
You said I was right.
He said yes.That's right.
But this is exactly the kind of thing that kids would love.
Why don't you bring the kids?
I don't have kids.
I don't have kids. I'm not lying.
People are aware of that.
Shall I show you the family register?
I don't have any! Prove it!
I'm not here.
I'm bringing him to my second son, who's just a little boy.
He's not here.
You're talking like you have a first son.
The second son is still tiny.
We don't have a first son or a second son.
She's asking if they're tiny.
I won't ask if he's tiny.
I won't say, "Do you have a family?
Your son...
Wow, he's good with paper.
He's coming over. He's stopping by.
It's closing time.
I see. It's closing time, and I say, "What are you doing here?
I'm just saying it's different.
I think you're looking at it too much.
I'm curious.
Is there some kind of special event today?
There's a camera crew.
Camera crew?
You-know-who is here.
I see. You mean "Thatchan"?
I know.
He knows.
Is that Jar Jar next to him?
He just got in.
I'm sorry to bother you. It's closing time.
What's going on? What's going on?What is it? Something's wrong.
What is that?
It's a decorator.
It's so tight.
It's amazing.
Is this what it looks like?
Just now?
They're only showing it now.
They brought it out. They brought out the decorator.
Thank you.
The decorator.
It's showing us everything.
It's lying down like this.
It's really showing off.
I'm glad you're here.
You can't see what I can't see.
I've never seen anything like it.
That's great. I'm so glad.
Thank you very much.
The decorating machine.
It's all wrapped up like this.
Oh, my God.
Let me see it right here.
It was a nice option.
Decorator option.
What's that? More cameras?
They've been back for a year.
That's good.
I didn't know it could be fixed.
Cameras?
I'll dry it off.
Then we came to a place called Tropical Island.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Tropical.
Tropical!Tropical.
That's what I'm talking about... this sandy beach.
Crabs?
Sandy beach.
Yes, but still...
Sandbox.
I feel like I'm going into the ocean.
It's like going into the water.
You can experience the feeling of going underwater.
This is also a well-calculated
It's an aquarium, isn't it?
I see what you mean.
It's pretty.
It's so cute, isn't it?
I like the black one.
It's so different from the one at the river.
It's so different.
It's just that the coral reefs...
The coral reef show is so brightly colored.
So the fish can hide in the coral reefs.
so that the fish can hide from the coral reefs.
to hide from the coral reefs.
I see.
So it's a coral match?
Tropical fish.
It's very characteristic.
Some of them are small.
That's nice.
Beautiful.
That's a big one.
There are so many different kinds of sparrows. They're so beautiful.
So cute.
I wonder if this is a horned snapper.
Beautiful.
I wonder.What's that?
Is it a hornfish?
Is it a horned bream?
What is it? Flying fish?
Looks like a flying fish.
It's coming this way.
I think it's a flying fish.
Next to a blowfish.
I wanted to see a blowfish.
Pufferfish are cute, aren't they?
He's got a blowfish key chain.
It's fine.
Nice.
Makes you want to go scuba diving, doesn't it?
You've actually dived in the ocean.
And see the scenery up close
Up close and personal
Right?
I don't think so.
So the aquarium is more like going to the ocean?
More than going to the ocean.
Do they go to the ocean more?
No, I go to the aquarium more.
It's hard to say.
I need more time.
What do you do after the aquarium?
I just...
I just sit and watch.
Look at all this stuff?
How long?
I stay as long as I can.
As long as the aquarium allows.
You're bothering me.
I'm sorry.
Until the aquarium says sorry.Until the aquarium says I'm sorry.
I'll be back before they tell me.
This one's completely different.
That's Dory, isn't it?
Nine hogfish.
That's a nine-tailed barnacle.
It's blue. I like blue.
You like blue?
Do you think it's pretty?
I'm glad you like it.
What's that?
I'm glad you think fish are cute.
Oh, my God.
Shall we go further?
There's something peculiar about the two of you.
Really?
The two male trapeze artists.
I see.
It's normal, but...
It's like a storyboard.
Like a storyboard?
It's like a picture show.
We're like a picture-story show.
I've never been told that before.
It's unique.
Even in this pitch-dark light.
It's too dark.
It's too much light.
I can't see anything.
There's a red one.
I know.
Red.
It's the first color
It's the first color to disappear.It's a color you'll lose, so fine.
If you're deep enough, you won't be able to see it.
That's why some fish
So there are fish with red bodies.
It's a beautiful red.
It means they're deep-sea fish.
That's what it means.
That's...
It's that deep.
You want to ask them?
Don't ask too many questions.
Listen.
I'll ask him.
It doesn't make any sense.
I don't need to know the whole story.
I'll ask you one time.
Here we go.
This is not a fish.
Hecko-ayu.
Hakoayu.
It's pointing vertically down.
The head is at the bottom.
It's mimicking seaweed.
You said it's flattened. - It's too flattened.
It's so flat that its head doesn't look like this.
It's too flat. It's not breathing.
But I don't know if it is.
We walk... we walk.
I'm walking upside down.
It's hekoayumu, isn't it?
So many colors
There's something that looks like a conger eel.
There's a dinga-anago
Silhouette
When going to Pokemon commercialWhen going Pokemon commercial
By the way, Chin is a
Chin is a Chinese dog.
There is a kind of dog called "Chin".
because it looks a little like a chinese dog.
Chin Anago.
Does it have a face?
Yes, it does.
They say so.
There are many theories.
I'll go further in.
What is it?
What's there?
Looks like a shrimp.
Lobsters?
Lobsters.
Lobsters!
Cool!
Lobsters are cool!
Lobsters are delicious.
Delicious!
Yum! Yum!
We had fried lobsters.
Lobsters at work.
My kids ate them.
Yum! Yum!
That's your dad!
My kid eats them.
I'm on location with my kid.
Dad!
The lobsters are so delicious.
You confessed.
I wonder...
It's so tiny!
What do you mean, "watermarked jersey bream"?Watermarked jersey bream means
Is it transparent or is the body
Not transparent.
Beautiful.
Transparent
Skeleton.
I like skeleton too.
They glow.
Game Boy.
Transparent ones.
Tamagotchi.
I like skeletons.
They're moving in clusters right now.
It's a goldfish.
This is a watermarked jersey bream.
Openwork Jersey bream...
The one on the far left
The one on the far left is a little stuck up and not moving much.
That's right.
If you thought it was a watermarked Jersey bream...
You're wrong.
The one in the back that's a little chunky...
Is the watermarked jersey bream.
And this one here...
is the one that's active.
It's the golden threadfin bream.
Mom and the sea bream
It's so nice to see you in front of me.
But you're beautiful.
beautiful, beautiful
Coral reef fish.
What? Oh, here.
Oh, here, dive for something.
I don't know.
Oh, here.Oh, here.
Climb up there and head on.
There it is.
Wow.
Whoa.
Why are you going first?
She's the one who's going.
That's right.
Why did you go first?
I got excited.
Sorry.
But I'm still going.
Wow!
Wow, this...
You know what?
It's like being under the sea.
It's an experience you're guaranteed to have.
Here you go.
Wow!
There's a shark in the foreground.
It might be a little scary.
Right in front of you.
It's right up there.
I didn't see it.
Scary.
Oh, my God.
Have fun.
Oh, my God, there's a shark right there.
I haven't seen a shark.
Take your time. Have fun.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
It's not going to attack you, so just take your time.
Into the water.
This is what the ocean tastes like.
I'm scared.I was scared.
I'm in the ocean.
Yeah, that's why.
It's like being in the ocean.
Underwater.
I'm scared of going underwater.
To go in the water.
I'm scared.
It's okay, your second time, take your time, don't say anything.
Hirai's second time is not like that.
No need, no need.
The second time, Hirai...
I don't need the second time.
Slowly.
Silent
Mute
No, wonderful, thank you
Thank you very much.
You're presenting us with all kinds of ways to showcase...
Well, let's all say thank you.
Let's all say thank you.
Thank you.
Let's move on.
Stop it.
It's a big tank.
Kamoshi.
This is it... the big tank... as I thought.
The sharks are already sleeping!
I'm tired.
I think he's sleeping.
He's tired and asleep.
It's nighttime.
Oh, hey.rough
Shark.
White.
It's white.
Yeah, it is.
What kind of shark is this?
What kind of shark?
A giant skateshark.
It's a giant axolotl.
Is it white originally?
Yes, this answer is a little bit white.
It means they are a little pale.
What would you do if you encountered one in the ocean?
Would you want to touch them?
You can't touch them.
From their point of view, it's like...
They might think you're trying to hurt them.
So you just watch them.
If you just watch them closely, it's probably okay.
Just like idols, right?
Yes, just to watch.
Just watching?
Don't try to do anything on your own.
You'll get in trouble.
You're a good fan.
Good fan.
You don't go to the beach much?
Not at all.
Except for work.
By myself.
That's why you guys with glasses...
Why do you go to the beach? Why do you want to go to the beach?
It's about time you called me a man-blanco.
I've always called you the man with the glasses.I've been calling him "the guy with the glasses.
I've been calling him "the guy with the glasses.
But to be honest, I don't go there for anything but diving.
I like the ocean.
But I don't like people who go to the ocean.
No, I get it. I get it.
Yeah, it's like...
It's like a "yay" kind of thing.
I don't like it either.
I don't like looking at the aquarium.
Yeah, it's nice.
I appreciate it more.
Thank you? Yeah, I'm glad.
Oh!
Tamakai?
Hata?
Tamakai, right?
The tamakai is very cool.
I love tamakai.
The big grouper.
What would you do if you met one of these in the ocean?
Scary.
Of course you'd be scared.
What's this?
Is that it?
Hanami scorpionfish.
It's big, but not for a flower-viewing scorpionfish.
Tiny.
I've seen it... the Hanami scorpionfish.
Scuba diving.
But all those spines are poisonous.
Don't touch them.
Never touch them.
They're like mascampi.
Punky.
It's interesting... all the different kinds.It's interesting... all the different kinds.
Here they come.
Interesting to see all the different kinds, isn't it?
I'm glad you're here.
Why's that?
I'm happy if you like it.
I'm flattered, but only if you're interested.
I mean, I'm an aquarium guy.
That's all I'm saying.
How was your day?
This duckweed...
How was it?
It was good.
For a very vague explanation.
I really enjoyed it.
Oh, that's good.
I love Animal House.
Animals is great, too.
Which one do you like better?
The aquarium or the zoo?
That's...
He asked me which I like better, curry or ramen.
I see.
Bad time
Animal Park.
I like Animal House just as much as you do.
Let me show you around.
Zoo.
Can you explain it to me a little more?
I beg you.
But I don't mind if you ask.
You know...
Subscribe to my channel.
I feel like we could be something, you and me.